https://go.navyonline.com/privacy-policy

Real Navy Gear. Real Navy Support.
Navyonline.com Privacy Policy
We know that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. By visiting Navyonline.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.
What Personal Information About You Does Navyonline.com Gather?
You can access our Website home page and browse our site without disclosing your personal information. The information we learn from Website visitors helps us personalize and continually improve your visit to Navyonline.com. Here are the types of information we gather.
Information You Give Us:
We receive and store any information you voluntarily enter on our Website or give us in any other way while using our services. For example, we request information on our order form such as your name, address, e-mail address, telephone and fax number, and credit card information. This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with you. We also use your name and address for Navyonline.com marketing purposes to notify you of our special offers and promotions.
Automatic Information:
We do not automatically collect personal information, nor do we link information automatically collected by other means with personal information about specific individuals.
Email Communications:
We collect personal information you may volunteer while using our services such as subscribing to the occasional e-mail communication regarding our site, special offers or services, products, events, or newsletters. You may choose to stop receiving them at any time by unsubscribing.
Information from Other Sources:
We do not collect information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records, public institutions or authorities, or private organizations.
What About Cookies?
A cookie is a piece of information stored on your computer's hard drive through your Web browser that contains information about you. We do not use cookies to store your personal information. We also do not link non-personal information stored in cookies with personal information about specific individuals.
Does Navyonline.com Share the Information It Receives?
Navyonline.com collects information from our visitors at several different points on our Website. Navyonline.com and the Naval Academy Business Services Division (NABSD) is the sole owner of this information. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this policy.
How Secure Is Information About Me?
We work to protect the security of your personal and credit card information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), 512 bit encryption software, which encrypts the personal and credit card information you input, provided your browser has this level of encryption. Also, remember to sign out of your account and close your browser windows when you finish surfing the Web, so that other people using the same computer won't have access to your information.
Your personal information includes items such as your name, address, telephone number, and other contact details. Credit card information includes your account number and expiration date.
We have implemented security policies, rules, and technical measures to protect the personal and credit card information under our control from loss, misuse, and alteration. All our employees and information processors who have access to and are associated with the processing of personal and credit card information are obligated to respect the confidentiality of your personal and credit card information.
We ensure that your personal and credit card information will not be disclosed to State or Federal government authorities unless required by applicable law or regulation.
What Information Can I Access?
You may request by e-mail, postal mail, or telephone whether we are keeping personal information about you. You also may request a readable copy of the personal information we keep about you, which we will provide to you within a reasonable time period of receiving your request. Although we may require proof of your identity before processing a request, we will provide the information without any charge. We reserve the right to refuse to provide our visitors with a copy of their personal information, but we will give reasons for our refusal.
What Choices Do I Have?
We allow you to challenge the data that we hold about you and, where appropriate, you may have the information erased, corrected, amended, or completed. We allow you to challenge our decision to refuse to provide you with a copy of your personal information.
Links
Navyonline.com occasionally may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of every website that collects personal or credit card information from you. This privacy policy solely applies to information collected by Navyonline.com.
Children's Privacy
The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act took effect on April 21, 2000. It imposes certain requirements on websites directed at children under 13 that collect information from those children, and on websites that knowingly collect information on children under 13. We do not knowingly collect information from children. If a child submits information to us through any part of our website, and we know that the person submitting the information is a child, we delete the information as soon as we discover it and do not use it for any purpose, nor do we disclose it to third parties. No one under the age of 15 should submit any personal information to this or any other website without the consent of a parent or guardian.
About Us
We pride ourselves in using modern information and communication technologies to provide tour and gift shop services to supporters of the U.S. Naval Academy through the Naval Academy Visitor Center. This policy covers the Naval Academy Business Services Division Website, Navyonline.com.
U.S. Naval Academy StoreNavyonline.com571 Kingwood StreetAnnapolis, Maryland 21402(410) 293-8126usnastore@usna.edu
Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions
By visiting Navyonline.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.
Our website does not enable our visitors to communicate with other visitors or to post information to be accessed by others. Our Website does not include links to third party Web service providers.
If we want to use your personal information for new purposes, we offer you the means to consent to those new purposes by indicating at the location on the Website where the personal information is collected, if possible, by e-mail, by postal mail, or by telephone.
If at any point we decide to use personal information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will not do so without first gaining your permission.
If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policy, please contact:
General ManagerU.S. Naval Academy StoreNavyonline.com571 Kingwood George Street Annapolis, MD 21402(410) 293-8126
Account
Privacy
Shipping
Returns
OPERATED BY NABSD | ALL PROCEEDS SUPPORT THE BRIGADE OF MIDSHIPMEN
Copyright , U.S. Naval Academy Store, All Rights Reserved.
